http://www.eibach.com/us/p-20-privacy-policy.html

Password
Forgot Password »
Street / Offroad
No attributes to narrow your search.- Year -- Make -- Model -- Selection -ClearSearch
Race Springs
All fields are optional
No attributes to narrow your search.- Diameter -- Length -- Rate -- Type -ClearSearch
UTV
No attributes to narrow your search.- UTV Year -- UTV Make -- UTV Model -- UTV Selection -ClearSearch
Moto
Select Moto
No attributes to narrow your search.- Moto Year -- Moto Make -- Moto Model -- Moto Selection -ClearSearch
Privacy Policy
Right to Know
We are committed to the privacy of your information. We do not, and will not, distribute, disclose or sell any of your personal information to third parties, other than as required by law or as necessary to process a payment.
As a user and/or consumer of Eibach, Inc., you have the right to know all personal information collected through our company and website (https://eibach.com/us/). To comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act, we have detailed the information below on how Eibach, Inc. collects, uses, discloses, and sells any personal information collected.
Submitting a Request for Your Collected Data
A request to view all personal information collected by Eibach, Inc. can be made using our Request for Personal Information form.
Data Request Verification Process
Eibach, Inc. requires verification of all personal information data requests before disclosing any data. The verification process may include matching identifying information provided by the consumer to information already collected by Eibach, Inc. (identifying purchases, order history, etc), responding to an email verification, or use of a third-party verification service.
Categories of Personal Information Collected
Eibach, Inc. collects the following personal information:
Identifiers - first and last name, email address, postal address, phone number, social media accounts, birth date, and order number(s).
Customer Records - first and last name,
email address, billing address, postal address, phone number, transaction ID, and IP address.
Eibach, Inc. does not store banking and/or credit card account numbers, as these are processed via a third party merchant service vendor.
Internet Activity - do tools like adroll and google using browser/search history and other web interactions need to be listed here?
Categories of Personal Information Sources
Eibach, Inc. collects personal information through placing orders, submitting web forms, creating accounts,employment applications, employment databses and use of the following 3rd party tools:
AdRoll -
Facebook Pixel -
Google -
YouTube -
Hotjar - website heatmaps and behavior analytics
Onepoint HCM
Purposes of Data Collection
Eibach, Inc. collects personal information for the following purposes: placing orders, event registration, displaying targeted advertisements, marketing campaigns, and responding to requests for disclosure of personal information collected.
Categories of Personal Information Recipients
Eibach, Inc. may disclose the following personal information to industry partners:
Identifiers: first and last name, email address, postal address, phone number
Personal Information Disclosure to 3rd Parties
Eibach, Inc. may disclose personal information to 3rd party tools to help us better understand consumer shopping experiences. This includes advertising networks, such as Google, Facebook, and AdRoll; data analytics providers such as Google Analytics; marketing email tools such as Mailchimp.
Eibach, Inc. uses Google Analytics for aggregated, anonymized website traffic analysis. In order to track session usage, Google uses a cookie (_ga) with a randomly-generated ClientID. This ID is anonymized and contains no identifiable information. We also send Google your IP address. Google Analytics helps us track website behavior so we can improve user experience and determine our site effectiveness. If you would like to access what browsing information we have - or delete any Google Analytics date - please delete your _ga cookies and/or opt out of tracking cookies on our site.
Eibach, Inc. uses NextRoll advertising network to track website behavior, what pages you viewed, and your IP address for display ad remarketing purposes. In order to track your session, NextRoll uses an anonymized cookie (consent/hod) which registers data on visitors to measure the efficiency of advertisements on websites. NextRoll’s Privacy Notice.
Categories of Personal Information Disclosed to 3rd Parties
Eibach, Inc. may disclose the following information to 3rd parties:
Internet or other electronic network activity including browsing history, search history, and interaction within our website.
Personal Information of Minors
Eibach, Inc. does not knowingly collect nor sell personal information of users under the age of 16 years without authorization.
Right to Deletion
As a consumer or visitor to Eibach, Inc. or eibach.com/us/, you have the right to request the deletion of any and all personal information collected by submitting a data deletion request.
Deletion of personal information is not required if Eibach, Inc. needs the information to complete the transaction for which it was collected; to comply with a legal obligation, such as a record retention requirement; to protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity; or to identify and repair errors that impair existing and intended functionality.
Verification Process
Eibach, Inc. has implemented a personal information verification process to ensure any requests for deleting personal information is made by the person of which the data is being deleted. Verification may include responding to an email sent to the identified email address or sending Eibach, Inc and customer order #.
Right to Opt-Out of the Sale of Personal Information
Eibach, Inc. does not sell any personal information to 3rd parties, however, as a consumer of Eibach, Inc., you have the right to opt-out of any personal information sale by submitting a Do Not Sell My Personal Information request form.
x
EIBACH INSIDER
Subscribe for the latest updates!
Subscribe
* indicates required
Email Address *
First name
Last name
Year
Make
Model
Manufacturing
Copyright © 2020 Eibach. All Rights Reserved.
Powered by Web Shop Manager.
California Consumer Privacy Act
We store consumer information on our website. If you continue without changing your settings, we will assume privileges to continue collection data during your visit on our site. Learn more.
I Understand
Decline
Loading Your Parts
×
